It's time for Enjoy Simple English! 森崎ウィンです
毎週火曜日は短編のショートコメディー カーメディスケッチーズ
今日は一人カラオケの魅力を語る話
ソロ・キャリオキー
そしてドッグ・トリーツ 犬用おやつの2話でございます
それではLet's listen together!
ソロ・キャリオキー
See you later. I'm going to karaoke.
Oh, who are you going with?
I'm going alone.
What?
I do it all the time.
Why do you go by yourself?
It's normal, Satoru.
No, it's not.
For karaoke, you need someone who sings and someone who listens.
If no one is listening, then it's no different from singing in the shower.
他の人とカラオケに行くときは 本当に彼らが歌うのを聞いているのですか?
友達と話して 食べて 飲んで
次の曲を選んでいるのかもしれませんよね?
まあ…お互いに言うことはあるかもしれませんが…
自分で行くときは 何曲も歌うことができます
あなたが悪いときでも
あなたの回りを待たなくても
一緒に一緒に歌うことができます
I see. But still, it's the same as singing in the shower.
Satoru, it's not the same.
Okay, let's go to karaoke together right now.
Together?
We'll go together, but get two rooms.
We will each do karaoke by ourselves.
It won't change my mind.
Just try it for an hour.
What is he doing?
すでに時間がかかっているのか?
前のデスクに聞いてみるよ
すみません、友達はまだ出てきていないの?
ああ、彼はもう1時間だけ歌ってほしいと言ってた
はっはっは、彼は気に入ってたわ
ドッグトリーズ
OK, Max. I'm going to throw this ball. So, go and get it. Are you ready?
Really? Are we doing this game again?
Max, get the ball!
I'm tired of this game. You threw it? Why do I have to go and get it?
Good boy! Great job! Here's your treat!
うぅ、クッキー?
クッキーよりビーフ・ジェルキーが好きなのかも知れませんね。
では、その箱を飛ばしてみましょう!
うぅ、うぅ、うぅ、
どうしよう、不可能だ!
それは高すぎる!
オリンピアンだと考えているのか?
マックス、飛び出せ!
行こう!
うぅ、うぅ、
私のオーナーは奇妙なアイデアを持っているのですが、ここから始めます。
私はこの大きな農園にどこかにビーフジャーキーを見つけたよ!
何?本当?
見つけろよ、マックス!
どこだ?どこだ?
ビーフジャーキーはどこだ?
見つけたよ!
木の中にあるものだ!
私にあげろ!私にあげろ!
いい子だ!
これがあなたのおやつだ!
クッキー!
文句を言いながらも走ってくれる犬
めちゃくちゃかわいいな
そしてカラオケいいですよね
You can sing any song even if you are bad at it
下手でもどんな歌でも歌える
このBad atはないないには下手
その逆はGood atないないは得意
はいいいですね使ってみましょう
それではI hope to see you tomorrow